<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CasualRP Podcast</title>
    <link>http://casualrp.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CasualRP Podcast</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>casualrp.podcast@gmail.com (Sean Stanley)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>casualrp.podcast@gmail.com (Sean Stanley)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 06:30:00 +1300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://casualrp.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>8 - Choosing Your Own Path</title>
      <link>http://casualrp.com/episodes/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 06:30:00 +1300</pubDate>
      <author>casualrp.podcast@gmail.com (Sean Stanley)</author>
      <guid>http://casualrp.com/episodes/8/</guid>
      <description>Attack! Furious and vicious small humanoids in masks leap from the jungle to attack the party. In the chaos, some of the prisoners make a run for freedom. But after the night&amp;rsquo;s battle, the party makes it to the seaside town of New Forlonde at last.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 - Disciples of The Raven Queen</title>
      <link>http://casualrp.com/episodes/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 09:31:46 +1300</pubDate>
      <author>casualrp.podcast@gmail.com (Sean Stanley)</author>
      <guid>http://casualrp.com/episodes/7/</guid>
      <description>The party finds themselves caught in the middle of someone else&amp;rsquo;s battle. Some humans with terrible fashion sense are being pursued by brightly coloured frog-people. The humans seek refuge with the party while the frog people attack indiscriminately. Cor however near the end of the fight decides to take the humans prisoner and the party then tries to figure out what to do with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 - Scars Are Just Another Kind of Memory</title>
      <link>http://casualrp.com/episodes/6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 06:30:00 +1300</pubDate>
      <author>casualrp.podcast@gmail.com (Sean Stanley)</author>
      <guid>http://casualrp.com/episodes/6/</guid>
      <description>The party passes near a magical tree bearing glowing Wucca nuts. Excited, the party climbs the tree and disturbs it&amp;rsquo;s inhabitants. The gold colored drop bears attack viciously and have some bizarre magical qualities. When the party camps to recover near a stream, a strange tri-flowered crawling plant approaches whose scent proves very alluring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 - This Jungle Is Nuts</title>
      <link>http://casualrp.com/episodes/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 06:30:00 +1300</pubDate>
      <author>casualrp.podcast@gmail.com (Sean Stanley)</author>
      <guid>http://casualrp.com/episodes/5/</guid>
      <description>Leila claims to not be human. Ser Selwyn doesn&amp;rsquo;t believe her. They visit a Craftsmen signal tower manned by the small Ganus family and meet the newest member little Letha. Ash, Ser Selwyn and Leila ask Penelope Ganus about the walking dead they saw and she provides some troubling information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 - The Aftermath</title>
      <link>http://casualrp.com/episodes/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 06:30:00 +1300</pubDate>
      <author>casualrp.podcast@gmail.com (Sean Stanley)</author>
      <guid>http://casualrp.com/episodes/3/</guid>
      <description>After the bar fight, Ser Selwyn talks to the guard about what to do with the Blackheart Orcs. Meanwhile Leila&amp;rsquo;s friends give her some advice on how to politically manage the situation. Ser Selwyn then goes over the details of the plan to retrieve the settlers with his superiors. They rest and rise extra early to depart Shinrin for the wild trails of the jungle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 - Enter the Blackhearts</title>
      <link>http://casualrp.com/episodes/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 06:30:00 +1300</pubDate>
      <author>casualrp.podcast@gmail.com (Sean Stanley)</author>
      <guid>http://casualrp.com/episodes/2/</guid>
      <description>Selwyn &amp;amp; Leila take a trip to the Kronus&amp;rsquo;s farm to try to convince the widow there to let her son join the Craftsmen. Meanwhile Ash takes Cor to a shrine to show him the deities of Shinrin. Cor isn&amp;rsquo;t much impressed. That evening, Leila&amp;rsquo;s friends are keen to meet Cor, for some reason, while Ash brags about becoming a Craftsman to the other guards. Their evening is interrupted by a gang of orcs called the Blackhearts looking for a fight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 - A Replacement Craftsman</title>
      <link>http://casualrp.com/episodes/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 06:30:00 +1300</pubDate>
      <author>casualrp.podcast@gmail.com (Sean Stanley)</author>
      <guid>http://casualrp.com/episodes/1/</guid>
      <description>After their tiger hunting trip, the party spends the evening dining with Lord Jacku and Lady Jiru Shinrin. The next morning they enjoy bacon in the servant&amp;rsquo;s kitchen before slipping out and splitting up to do town jobs. Ser Selwyn &amp;amp; Leila visit Ser Thomas while Cor &amp;amp; Ash go shopping for supplies with their new-found wealth. They learn about a job escorting new settlers to Shinrin and decide to take it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://casualrp.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>casualrp.podcast@gmail.com (Sean Stanley)</author>
      <guid>http://casualrp.com/about/</guid>
      <description>The Jungle Campaign follows a boy, guard, thief and giant as they are caught between the wild cries of the jungle and the hammers of industry.
Originally The Jungle Campaign began with Sean running a home game for Travis, Jasher, Hamish, Caleb, and Hope, but eventually it evolved into a D&amp;amp;D real-play podcast.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>